http://www.cadillacnews.com/site/terms.html

Reader Rewards
Advertise with Us!
Reader Rewards
Advertise with Us!
Home
cadillacnews.com is a community Web site for Wexford County, Missaukee County, Osceola County, Lake County, and surrounding areas, operated by The Cadillac News. These terms apply to any part of our websites including cadillacnews.com, weeklyvoice.net, and askrover.info. These websites provides members and other visitors to our site a forum for sharing comments, photos, event listings and other content. Please read the rules contained in this agreement. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Web site constitutes your agreement to comply with these rules. Because the Internet is an evolving medium, we may need to change these Terms of Use from time to time. Changes will be posted to this Terms of Use and the effective date of the terms will reflect the date of the changes.Disclaimer and Visitor’s AgreementMaterials that are submitted are not endorsed by The Cadillac News. The Cadillac News does not guarantee the accuracy of information posted in our forums, whether that information comes from a user, local official, celebrity, "expert" or a member of our own staff.There is no substitute for healthy skepticism and your own good judgment when reading forum posts.Limitations on our liabilityUnder no circumstances shall The Cadillac News be held liable to damages arising from this web site stemming from the forums module.RegistrationVisitors thirteen years of age or older who agree to the Terms of Service may register and post content to the site. To register you will be asked to choose a username and provide a valid email address. You agree that the information you supply will be accurate and that you will not supply the email address of, or register under the name of, another person. We reserve the right to reject any username we deem offensive or inappropriate.Privacy PolicyWe respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.  This personal information can include, but is not limited to, you Name, Phone Number, Address, Location, Banking Information, Bowser information, IP Address, and Cookie information.We respect your privacy and will never sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share your personal information with anyone without your consent. This information will never be used to send spam.Cadillacnews.com collects user-submitted information such as email addresses to authenticate users. cadillacnews.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to track usage of the website and improve services. This aggregated data may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant and targeted advertisements or services to users.A valid email address is required to register with the site. At no time will your email address be shared with a third party without your consent.Cadillacnews.com will set a cookie that identifies you when you log in to the site. This is necessary to maintain your preferences and to prevent you from having to log in to every page.When purchasing a service from our website, your banking information is passed directly to the processing institution, and is not retained on our website. Security PolicyYour payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.Use of Communication ServicesWe may provide areas on this Web site allowing our users to interact with others through modules such as forums, blogs, classified advertisements, user submitted photos and public areas. As a community oriented newspaper company we believe in the promotion of free speech and the open exchange of information and ideas through the medium of the Internet and through other channels. We want all of our readers to be able to enjoy our communications services available at cadillacnews.com.We reserve the right to deny access to our communications services to any visitor who violates the "Terms of Use" or who we believe to interfere with the daily operation of this site's communications services.We also reserve the right to delete, move, edit and filter any posts to our communications services that come to our attention that we find unacceptable or inappropriate, whether for legal or other reasons. We will comply with the requirement of the law concerning the disclosure of communications services messages posted by our users to others, including law enforcement agencies.Posting ContentWe have a few simple rules for posting content. We reserve the right to delete any content that doesn’t follow these rules, and to terminate the accounts of anyone who repeatedly violates them.Please be responsible. Self-moderate, remembering that this is a family Web site. Don’t post content you wouldn’t want your 13-year-old child or your mother to view. That includes profanity, nudity and lewdness.Any content you post anywhere on cadillacnews.com must be your original work, or you must have authorization from the copyright owner. Do not attempt to impersonate another individual.Do not post content that defames or invades the privacy of an individual. Keep your disagreements civil. No harassing or intimidating others. Disagree with another person’s views – don’t attack the person.Keep your ranting to a minimum. Take a deep breath, count to 10.Try to keep your posts on topic as much as possible.Content that promotes racism, bigotry, homophobia, hatred or physical harm to any group or individual will not be tolerated.Content posted to cadillacnews.com is not screened or edited by us, and we make no claims as to the validity or accuracy of content posted. Under no circumstances is The Cadillac News liable in any way for the content that is posted by users.The Web site is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under the copyright laws of the United States and other countries. All individual articles, content and other elements comprising this Web site are also copyrighted works.By posting content to the Web site, you automatically grant the right to The Cadillac News to use, copy, modify, adapt or publish the content that you post, including for purposes of advertising and publicity on the Web site and elsewhere. The Cadillac News is under no obligation to pay you for your posting.Examples of Prohibited UsesThe following, may constitute the deleting of a post or the removal of a user.Uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available any content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, libelous, or obscene;Impersonating any person or entity, or falsely stating or otherwise misrepresenting your affiliation with a person or entity;Forging headers or otherwise manipulating identifiers in a manner that disguises the origin of any content you transmit through any Communications Service;Uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available any content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary right of any party;Uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, or any other form of solicitation, without our expressed written consent;Gathering for the purpose of "spamming" any email addresses that users post in our chat rooms, forums and other public posting areas;Uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available any content or material that contains software viruses, worms or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications or other equipment, or to cause a security breach of such software, hardware or telecommunications or other equipment;Uploading or posting any off-topic or irrelevant material to any forum or comment area;Interfering with or disrupting any servers or networks used to provide the Communications Services, or disobeying any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of the networks we use to provide the Communications Services;"Stalking" or otherwise harassing another user;Instigating or encouraging others to commit illegal activities or cause injury or property damage to any person;Gaining unauthorized access to our website, or any account, computer system, or network connected to this website, by means such as hacking, password mining or other illicit means; orObtaining or attempting to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through this Web site.Disclaimer of WarrantiesYou agree that use of the cadillacnews.com web site and any material or information available through this site is entirely at your own risk. This site is provided by cadillacnews.com on an "as is" and "as available" basis.cadillacnews.com makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of this site or the accuracy, completeness, currentness, non-infringement, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose of the information available through this site, nor do we guarantee that the site will be error-free, continuously available, or free of viruses or other harmful components.Under no circumstances will cadillacnews.com or its affiliates, agents, employees, representatives or licensors be liable to you or anyone else for any damages, other than direct damages, arising out of your use of this web site or any product or service linked to, from or advertised or promoted on this web site.You agree to indemnify and hold harmless cadillacnews.com, its affiliates, agents, employees, representatives and licensors against any liability of any nature arising out of any content posted on the cadillacnews.com site by you or by others using your account.
Latest News
Asian stocks mixed after Wall St falls on virus pressure
Michigan expects 257,000 COVID-19 vaccine doses initially
Biden's transition contends with probe into son's finances
Sen. Rand Paul delays defense bill vote over troop drawdowns
In Arizona, Trump's false claims have torn open a GOP rift
Congress stuck, McConnell resists state aid in COVID-19 deal
AP News in Brief at 12:04 a.m. EST
Global Anti-plagiarism Software Market to Have Positive Impact Due to COVID-19 Spread | Proliferation of Online Assignment & Project Submission Platforms to Boost Growth | Technavio
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesMSP: Standoff ends after suspect takes own lifePolice, neighbors putting pieces together after deadly standoffAs COVID hospitalizations ramp up, hospital employees band together to combat stress, exhaustionMcBain man sentenced after CSC convictionsShelly M. AllenSuspect arrested after hit and run, crash Saturday in Wexford CountyThomas J MoomeyCadillac man charged with retail fraudMSP: Standoff ends after suspect takes own lifePolice respond to reports of vehicle 'all over the roadway,' arrest Muskegon man
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Stocks
Market Data by TradingView
© Copyright 2020 Cadillac News, 130 N Mitchell St PO Box 640 Cadillac, MI | Terms of Use
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
